Guide to the D'Arcy Masius Benton & Bowles archives, 1929-1995 and undated RL.00314
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Advertisements, 1932-1995
  - Oversized Materials
    - Western Electric
      - 1959-1962, Consumer and trade newspaper (Box OV16)
    - West Point Pepperell
      - 1944-1948, Trade newspaper (Box OV17)
      - 1945, Trade magazine (Box OV17)
      - 1945-1959, Consumer magazine (Box OV17)
      - 1948-1951, Trade magazine (Box OV17)
      - 1949-1951, Trade newspaper (Box OV17)
      - 1952-1953, Trade newspaper (Box OV17)
      - 1954, Consumer and trade (Box OV17)
      - 1955-1958, Trade magazine (Box OV17)
      - 1955-1959, Trade newspaper (Box OV17)
      - 1959-1961, Trade magazine (Box OV17)
      - 1961-1964, Consumer magazine (Box OV17)
      - 1961-1968, Trade newspaper (Box OV17)
      - 1962-1965, Trade magazine (Box OV17)
      - 1967-1968, Consumer magazine (Box OV17)
    - Yardley of London
      - 1970-1971, Consumer magazine (Box OV17)
      - 1972, Consumer newspaper (Box OV17)
- Audiovisual Materials, ca. 1950-1986
  The films listed are believed all to predate 1986. Some material probably dates from the 1950s, with the bulk being from the 1960s-1970s. The films are arranged in numerical order by the reel number. Some individual cans contain detailed contents lists. For others, the content information is limited to a summary statement such as Charmin Historical Reel.
  Conditions Governing Access note
  Original film reels are restricted until use copies are made. Digitized versions of many reels are available in the AdViews Digital Collection. Some physical use copies are available in the collection, and have been noted where available. Contact Research Services for further information.
  - Originals (Closed to Research)
    - Birdseye (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 1)
    - Alpha Bits (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 2)
    - Peter Paul (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 3)
    - Toastem's (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 4)
    - Raisin Bran (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 5)
    - Avis (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 6)
    - Yardley (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 7)
    - Allied Chemical (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 8)
    - Dana (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 9)
    - Eastern Airlines (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 10)
    - Schick
      - Schick #4 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 11)
      - Schick #3 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 12)
      - Schick #2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 13)
      - Schick #1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 14)
    - GCMI
      - GCMI #1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 15)
      - GCMI #2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 16)
    - Florida Citrus
      - Florida Citrus #1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 17)
      - Florida Citrus #2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 18)
      - Florida Citrus #3 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 19)
    - Miscellaneous (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 20)
    - Beechnut Candy (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 21)
    - Beech Nut
      - Beech Nut Food Processing (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 22)
      - Beech Nut Lifesaver Cough Drops (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 23)
      - Beech Nut Gum & Lifesavers (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 24)
    - S.C. Johnson
      - S.C. Johnson Compiled #1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 25)
      - S.C. Johnson Compiled #3 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 26)
      - S.C. Johnson Compiled #4 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 27)
      - S.C. Johnson Compiled #5 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 28)
      - S.C. Johnson Compiled #6 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 29)
      - S.C. Johnson Compiled #7 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 30)
      - S.C. Johnson Compiled #8 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 31)
      - S.C. Johnson Compiled #9 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 32)
      - S.C. Johnson Miscellaneous (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 33)
    - Sodaburst (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 34)
    - Maxwell House
      - Instant Maxwell House--Joel Cheek (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 35)
      - Instant Maxwell House #2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 36)
      - Instant Maxwell House #4 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 37)
      - Instant Maxwell House #5 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 38)
      - Instant Maxwell House #7 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 39)
      - Instant Maxwell House #8 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 40)
      - Instant Maxwell House #14 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 41)
    - Ansco
      - Ansco #1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 42)
      - Ansco #2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 43)
    - Miscellaneous Historical--Good Measure, Birdseye (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 44)
    - Texaco
      - Texaco #10 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 45)
      - Texaco #11 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 46)
      - Texaco #12 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 47)
      - Texaco #13 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 48)
    - Beech Nut
      - Beech Nut Gum (B & W) (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 49)
      - Beech Nut Gum (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 50)
      - Beech Nut Compiled (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 51)
      - Beech Nut Baby Food (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 52)
      - Beech Nut Baby Foods (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 53)
      - Beech Nut Gum & Candy (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 54)
    - Borden
      - Borden #1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 55)
      - Borden #2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 56)
      - Borden #3 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 57)
    - Squibb
      - Squibb #1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 58)
      - Squibb #2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 59)
      - Squibb #3 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 60)
    - Carlings
      - Carlings #1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 61)
      - Carlings #2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 62)
      - Carlings #3 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 63)
    - Utica Club (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 64)
    - ASRI (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 65)
    - ASR (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 66)
    - Kent (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 67)
    - Philip Morris
      - Parliament #1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 68)
      - Parliament #2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 69)
      - Parliament #3 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 70)
      - Parliament #4 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 71)
      - Parliament #5 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 72)
      - Parliament #6 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 73)
      - Parliament #7 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 74)
    - Chemical Bank (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 75)
    - Chemical Bank (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 76)
    - Camay (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 77)
    - MONY #1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 78)
    - Best Foods (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 79)
    - Anderson Clayton #1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 80)
    - Anderson Clayton #2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 81)
    - American Motors
      - American Motors #1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 82)
      - American Motors #2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 83)
      - American Motors #3 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 84)
    - Pream 1 (Box OV17, Reel 85)
    - Pream 2 (Box OV17, Reel 86)
    - Studebaker 1 (Museum of Broadcasting) (Box OV17, Reel 87)
    - Studebaker 2 (Museum of Broadcasting) (Box OV17, Reel 88)
    - Yuban
      - Yuban 1 (Box OV17, Reel 89)
      - Yuban 2 (Box OV17, Reel 90)
      - Yuban 3 (Box OV17, Reel 91)
      - Yuban 4 (Box OV17, Reel 92)
    - Kentile, Heublein, Desert Dri, Western Union (Box OV17, Reel 93)
    - Shulton 1 (Box OV17, Reel 94)
    - Canada Dry 1 (Box OV17, Reel 95)
    - Paxten-Saratoga (Box OV17, Reel 96)
    - American Express (Box OV17, Reel 97)
    - Fluffo 1 (Box OV17, Reel 98)
    - Merrill (Box OV17, Reel 99)
    - Texaco 1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 100)
    - Texaco 2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 101)
    - General Foods Miscellaneous (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 102)
    - B & B (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 103)
    - Benton & Bowles
      - B & B Compiled #2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 104)
      - B & B Compiled #6 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 105)
      - B & B Compiled #12 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 106)
      - B & B Compiled #15 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 107)
      - B & B Compiled #21 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 108)
      - B & B Compiled #24 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 109)
    - Vintage Television
      - Linus--Visiting Children's Show (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 110)
      - Linus #21 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 111)
      - Linus Pilot (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 112)
      - Grindl (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 113)
      - Barbara Rush (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 114)
      - Dr. Who: The End of Tomorrow: BBC (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 115)
      - Edge of Night (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 116)
      - Dick Van Dyke (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 117)
      - Kentucky Jones (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 118)
      - Down You Go (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 119)
    - Pampers
      - Pampers 1975 (800' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 120)
      - Pampers #2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 121)
      - Pampers #4 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 122)
      - Pampers #4 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 123)
      - Pampers #5 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 124)
      - Pampers #6 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 125)
      - Pampers #6 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 126)
      - Pampers #10 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 127)
      - Pampers #11 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 128)
      - Pampers #11 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 129)
    - Texaco
      - Reel #14 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 130)
      - Reel #15 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 131)
      - Reel #16 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 132)
      - Reel #7A (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 133)
      - Reel #9A (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 134)
      - Foreign (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 135)
    - Crest--Bill Cosby (400' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 136)
      [Use Copy UC13 in collection]
    - Gillette (800' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 137)
    - Good News (800' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 138)
    - Crest
      - Crest #23 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 139)
        [Use Copy UC20 in collection]
      - Crest #24 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 140)
      - Crest #25 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 141)
        [Use Copy UC21 in collection]
      - Crest #26 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 142)
    - Gillette
      - Gillette Good News (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 143)
      - Gillette and Peter Paul (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 144)
      - Gilette Trac II (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 145)
    - Gravy Train
      - Gravy Train Historical (800' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 146)
      - Gravy Train 2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 147)
      - Gravy Train R-5 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 148)
    - Rally (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 149)
    - Cool Whip #3 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 150)
    - Gaines
      - Gaines Historical #3 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 151)
      - Gaines Meal 1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 152)
      - Gaines Meal 2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 153)
      - Gaines 4 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 154)
      - Gaines Miscellaneous (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 155)
      - Gaines (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 156)
    - Post
      - Post Miscellaneous #2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 157)
      - Post Historical #1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 158)
      - Post Historical Miscellaneous (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 159)
      - Puffed Corn (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 160)
      - Alpha Bits 4 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 161)
      - Alpha Bits 5 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 162)
      - Raisin Bran #2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 163)
      - Raisin Bran #3 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 164)
      - Grape Nuts #3 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 165)
      - Grape Nuts #5 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 166)
    - Crest
      - Mr. Goodwin Outtakes--35mm (4 rolls) (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 167)
      - Crest Historical #10 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 168)
        [Use Copy UC14 in collection]
      - Crest Historical #14 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 169)
        [Use Copies UC16, UC17 in collection]
      - Crest Historical #15 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 170)
        [Use Copy UC17 in collection]
      - Crest Historical #16 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 171)
        [Use Copies UC17, UC18 in collection]
      - Crest Historical#17 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 172)
        [Use Copy UC18 in collection]
      - Crest Historical#18 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 173)
      - Crest Historical#19 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 174)
        [Use Copy UC19 in collection]
      - Crest Historical #20 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 175)
      - Crest Historical #21 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 176)
      - Crest Historical #22 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 177)
    - Post Tens (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 178)
    - Brim (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 180)
    - Brim (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 181)
    - Schlitz (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 182)
    - Yuban (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 183)
    - Bounce
      - Bounce #1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 184)
      - Bounce #5 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 185)
        (NOTE: Bounce 2-4 missing)
      - Bounce #6 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 186)
    - Norwich
      - Norwich #1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 187)
      - Norwich #2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 188)
      - Norwich #3 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 189)
      - Norwich #4 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 190)
      - Norwich #5 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 191)
      - Norwich #6 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 192)
      - Norwich #7 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 193)
      - Norwich #8, 9 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 194)
      - Norwich #10 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 195)
    - Libra #1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 196)
    - Milliken Visa (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 197)
    - Horizon Historical (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 198)
    - Robert Hall (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 199)
    - N.B. Toy (?) Reel, 1982 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 200)
    - IBM #1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 201)
    - New Age Historical #1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 202)
    - Orange Plus
      - Orange Plus 1 of 3 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 203)
      - Orange Plus 2 of 3 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 204)
      - Orange Plus 3 of 3 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 205)
    - Digital Historical Reel #1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 206)
    - Vicks
      - Vicks 1986 to Present (Nyquil Historical Reel) (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 207)
      - Woody Woodpecker (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 208)
      - Vaporub 1 of 3 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 209)
      - Vaporub 2 of 3 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 210)
      - Vaporub 3 of 3 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 211)
      - Vicks #1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 212)
      - Vicks #2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 213)
      - Vicks #3 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 214)
      - Vicks #4 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 215)
      - Vicks #5 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 216)
    - Ivory Snow--Miscellaneous (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 217)
    - Echrich (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 218)
    - SIA (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 219)
    - General Foods--Candy #1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 220)
    - Marine Midland (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 221)
    - Orange Twist (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 222)
    - Bonus (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 223)
    - Hardee's
      - Hardees Miscellaneous #2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 224)
      - Hardees Miscellaneous #3 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 225)
      - Hardees Miscellaneous #4 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 226)
    - Grape Nuts #1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 227)
    - Grape Nuts #2A (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 228)
    - Crest--circa Pool, A,M. Dental (200' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 229)
      [Use Copy UC11 in collection]
    - Alpha Bits #3 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 230)
    - Texaco #8 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 231)
    - Crest, Triumph, Tooth Decay (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 232)
      [Use Copy UC15 (Crest) in collection]
    - Toasties #3 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 233)
    - Dawn (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 234)
    - Post Miscellaneous #6 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 235)
    - D'Arcy Compilation (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 236)
    - Crest #2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 237)
      [Use Copy UC10 in collection]
    - Crest #11 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 238)
      [Use Copies UC14, UC15 in collection]
    - Hasbro
      - Hasbro #1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 239)
      - Hasbro #2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 240)
      - Hasbro #3 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 241)
      - Hasbro #4 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 242)
      - Hasbro #5 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 243)
      - Hasbro #6 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 244)
    - Sugar Crisp #4 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 245)
    - Vicks #6 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 246)
    - Continental 1 of 2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 247)
    - Continental 2 of 2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 248)
    - Skillet #1, 1959 (100' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 249)
    - Stockholders' Meeting, 1981 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 250)
    - Stockholders' Meeting (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 251)
    - AMF Corporate Film, 1976 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 252)
    - AMF Corporate Film 1977 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 253)
    - Europe Reel--Roy Bostock 1981 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 254)
    - Pampers
      - Pampers #7 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 255)
      - Pampers #8 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 256)
      - Pampers #12 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 257)
    - Dawn
      - Dawn #2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 258)
      - Dawn #3 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 259)
      - Dawn #4 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 260)
    - Vintage Television Shows
      - Phil Silvers (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 261)
      - Sgt. Bilko (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 262)
      - Summer Playhouse (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 263)
      - Sgt. Bilko, Viva Bilco (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 264)
    - Post
      - Grape Nuts #4 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 265)
      - Grape Nuts #2B (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 266)
      - Grape Nuts Historical Reel A (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 267)
    - Fiat 1 of 2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 268)
    - Fiat 2 of 2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 269)
    - Ferrari (800' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 270)
    - Ivory Snow
      - Ivory Snow #1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 271)
      - Ivory Snow #2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 272)
      - Ivory Snow #3 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 273)
      - Ivory Snow #4 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 274)
      - Ivory Snow #5 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 275)
      - Ivory Snow #6 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 276)
      - Ivory Snow #7 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 277)
      - Ivory Snow #8 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 278)
      - Ivory Snow #9 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 279)
      - Ivory Snow #10 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 280)
    - McCulloch 1 of 2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 281)
    - McCulloch 2 of 2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 282)
    - Pinkerton (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 283)
    - Scope
      - Scope #1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 284)
        [Use Copy UC25 in collection]
      - Scope #2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 285)
        [Use Copy UC26 in collection]
      - Scope #3 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 286)
        [Use Copy UC27 in collection]
      - Scope #4 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 287)
        [Use Copy UC28 in collection]
      - Scope #5 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 288)
        [Use Copy UC29 in collection]
      - Scope #6 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 289)
        [Use Copy UC30 in collection]
      - Scope #7 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 290)
        [Use Copy UC31 in collection]
    - Vintage Television Shows
      - Red Buttons (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 291)
      - Jackie Robinson (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 292)
      - Paul Winchell (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 293)
      - Sgt. Bilko 1 of 6 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 294)
      - Sgt. Bilko 2 of 6 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 295)
      - Sgt. Bilko 3 of 6 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 296)
      - Sgt. Bilko 4 of 6 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 297)
      - Sgt. Bilko 5 of 6 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 298)
      - Sgt. Bilko 6 of 6 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 299)
      - Sgt. Bilko 1 of 7 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 300)
      - Sgt. Bilko 2 of 7 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 301)
      - Sgt. Bilko 3 of 7 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 302)
      - Sgt. Bilko 4 of 7 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 303)
      - Sgt. Bilko 5 of 7 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 304)
      - Sgt. Bilko 6 of 7 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 305)
      - Sgt. Bilko 7 of 7 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 306)
    - F.O.F. Historical (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 307)
    - F.O.F. Historical #1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 308)
    - Sara Lee (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 309)
    - Hardees Miscellaneous (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 310)
    - Liquid Prell (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 311)
    - Charmin Historical #4 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 312)
      [Use Copy UC4 in collection]
    - Crum & Forster (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 313)
    - Corning (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 314)
    - Whipped Cream (Birdseye) (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 315)
    - Hutton (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 316)
    - Hanes Laura (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 317)
    - Texaco
      - Presentation--Vic Bloedes (400' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 318)
      - Commercial International (800' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 319)
      - Miscellaneous 1 of 2 (800' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 320)
      - Miscellaneous 2 of 2 (800' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 321)
      - Texaco #1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 322)
      - Texaco #2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 323)
      - Texaco #3 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 324)
      - Texaco #4 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 325)
      - Texaco #6 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 326)
      - Texaco #7 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 327)
    - Various Commercials
      - SPI Standard Peel (800' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 328)
      - Compiled--Sheldon Platt (800' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 329)
      - Ivory Snow Historical #1 (800' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 330)
      - AMC (800' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 331)
      - IBM (800' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 332)
      - Sgt. Bilko (Carling) (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 333)
      - Cereal (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 334)
      - GTI (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 335)
      - S.C. Johnson's (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 336)
    - Post
      - Honey Comb (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 337)
      - Post Miscellaneous #8 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 338)
      - Honey Comb #1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 339)
      - Toasties #2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 340)
      - Toasties #4 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 341)
      - Post Tens (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 342)
      - Pebbles 1 of 2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 343)
      - Pebbles 2 of 2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 344)
      - Puffed Corn Flakes II (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 345)
      - 40% Bran (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 346)
    - Sheldon Platt Sample (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 347)
    - Standard Reel #5 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 348)
    - Charmin
      - Charmin #1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 349)
        [Use Copy UC1 in collection]
      - Charmin #2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 350)
        [Use Copy UC2 in collection]
      - Charmin #3 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 351)
        [Use Copy UC3 in collection]
      - Charmin #5 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 352)
        [Use Copy UC5 in collection]
      - Charmin #6 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 353)
        [Use Copy UC6 in collection]
      - Charmin #7 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 354)
        [Use Copy UC7 in collection]
      - Charmin #8 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 355)
        [Use Copy UC8 in collection]
      - Charmin #9 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 356)
        [Use Copy UC9 in collection]
    - Brim (800' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 357)
    - Honeycomb #2 Historical (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 358)
    - Bounce (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 359)
    - Wondra (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 360)
    - Brim Historical Reel #2 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 361)
    - Everything Reel--Spain, 1977 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 362)
    - Visit U.S.A. (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 363)
    - Planters (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 364)
    - December Bride (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 365)
    - Paging Women (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 366)
    - Crest
      - Crest #1 (1500' reel) (Box OV17, Reel 367)